Heat.
Hello. Hello. Coma.
[laughter]
Don't Don't mind the gifted uh thingy I
just did. [music]
Um I gave a gifted sub to myself. a node
myself to someone in the community. I
think honorable son got
the gifted sub. Let's go.
Yay. Congratulations.
I wanted the Warog's golden badge, so
I ended up gifting someone in the
community.
So, yeah. Enjoy the gifted sub.
Hello everyone.
So today is the last day for Warog's
beta, open beta, and it's going to end
in in uh 2 hours from now. I'm a bit
late to start the stream today, but it's
fine.
And I'm in the middle of um eating as
well.
So, there's that as well. Hi. Let's
enjoy and have fun today.
All right.
Uh give me a minute.
Give me a minute. Let me just
let me just do some stuff.
Uh
wait.
Okay, we should be good. And
we're live on all platforms. Yep, we're
live. Live live.
Wait, I was watching some tutorials on
how to do the
helicopter flying the pilot class stuff.
Um, so there's that.
I'll eventually learn, so it's fine.
Uh,
I I'm in the middle of eating, too. So,
I'll eat that. Uh, give me a minute. I
may switch.
Wait. So, before we get into this, I
wanted to
go to the firing range.
go to the firing range and then practice
help to fly.
We'll change some settings and
everything and then we go get into the
battlefield.
Let's go to the vehicle.
Look what the cated
spend money to make money.
Incident
helicopter
pilot. Before we start, I need to change
some settings on controller
control settings.
Rook on by default
sensitivity,
flight assist. Oh, everything is
enabled.
Round car.
Oh, this is like battlefield.
Oh.
Uh, that didn't go well. Okay, another
retry.
Want to try something new?
>> What if I ask him for this money
>> so I can
go all the way here? I mean, that's
unnecessary, but I don't move.
Okay, this is this is dumb.
Ah,
wait.
Let me watch that tutorial again.
All access
So, what's it going to be?
>> Okay, this should work. [panting]
Okay, I'm slowly getting control of it.
Go
a fly up
helicopter. It's hard.
I like to see another one.
>> So, what's it going to be?
around.
Come back anytime.
>> Oh, this is the big fighter air compact
plane.
Oh, yeah. It is
with like missiles and stuff.
Oh, it has like a opposite
Oh, this is nice.
Okay. Slowly.
Okay. If it's if I'm not using mouse to
yaw and
uh rotate, I am able to actually pull it
off. Well,
okay, never mind.
And now the next thing I need to learn
is landing
from high speed to landed correctly in a
point.
I'm going back.
Wait.
What are you after?
Oh, I can buy this stuff
Sure.
Alexa, that is the coordinates I have to
go.
I'll try to practice going there.
I let the wind take me and ride me.
Okay. And let's assume that
let's assume that this field is where
I'm dropping. So I'll control and lower
the speed.
and try to land the plane safely.
Damn, I'm able to do it correctly.
Hey, I think we should be good. If I do
it like that properly,
maybe I can do transportation
for players.
Hey,
let's get on this one. 15.
Wait.
And we are loading in. Nice.
Okay, I'll go join the red faction.
Okay, let's go.
Why is it always me who have to say
hello? Hey,
>> see you around.
>> We can just take someone else's bed load
out, maybe.
Bro, I can't move.
Move you guys.
I my helicopter is
Yeah, I have not gone.
No parachute.
Let's give it our best.
If one of these guys die, I'll just loot
their dead body and make some money.
[\h__\h]
I took me.
Oh my god.
Okay, there is team kill. Oh [\h__\h]
Jocknik's [\h__\h]
cute. Oh my god, he's the Oh my
Oh my god.
>> What is that Chinese thingy? Oh my
Oh my god. What the [\h__\h]
Transport. Stop.
It sucks that I have to explain myself
like this.
Tinies.
Your wife
grass.
meaning in
Good job.
I love you.
Seriously,
another What?
Huh?
Okay, everyone. I'm back. Okay. Um, that
was awkward.
What just happened earlier,
bro? I wanted to go no load out and like
get load out from enemy. I ended up
and not me but yeah,
I accidentally ended up killing
teammate.
Okay, that was a sneaky brat.
Go on, treat yourself.
What do you
daddy?
I've never
There are a bunch of people around.
I'm bleeding out over here.
Uh, deep.
Let me remove that guy.
enemy
and blue team. Blue team.
Come on.
She's
Come Bly over here.
Okay, let's go back to base and
kill.
Oh, you sort of got in it.
to get
Okay, my plan is to infiltrate the green
tower,
get a few kills.
Oh my god, there they're sending the
alter everyone.
One way
I can stay here and like
the thing is this guy is trying to get
here.
They have a tank.
Someone outside here.
There's this one guy
probably sniping.
>> Sit tight. I'm inbound.
I will let I will let someone go.
We let someone go. Nice.
Enemy
trucks Coming this way.
They're going to the
Solid work.
Where are the people? Oh [\h__\h] SM
me from the sky.
Nope. No one's going to come.
But we made $10,000.
That's nice.
>> You know the score. Buy what you want
and [\h__\h] off.
>> So this time I'll just do
>> pilot thing. Maybe
>> you want it, you buy it.
Stay around.
All
right.
Okay.
Oh, just like we've read this slow and
steady
Okay,
that was good. Good. uh drop off.
Now we go back and get some more stuff.
Okay, good landing.
Uh
the refering. Okay.
Explain this.
Okay.
Okay, I have to
I have to lower the speed.
Okay, good.
I'm making a lot of profit,
which is really nice.
I'm
I don't even
Okay, next round trip.
Well, that was scary. I almost hit the
trees.
You didn't notice.
What's
good?
Ah, my money.
My money.
We do it.
I jump.
I'll deploy over there since I lost my
stuff. And I'll just
uh put all the supplies into the fob.
That way I can
get most of the stuff done.
Ah, these aren't mine. Ah,
what the
h? I don't have a backpack. I forgot.
I do not have a Mac pack.
Let him unload. I'll unload this.
And why did no one take that over.
That is so weird.
I had this little backpacks
could have done Then
heat.
Yeah, I have to
somehow return to spawn.
Are you going to buy something?
>> Oh, 15 slots. 12 slots. 21 swords,
medium tag.
Don't let me down.
Who is this echo dude?
Bro, he's he had he has made 72,000
$74,640
profit.
Ah, crazy.
How are these people getting so much
profit?
the oil and stuff.
Bring it.
Um,
this one's not
I need to unlock the RPG
somehow.
Artisia's best.
Mirror
def.
This guy is doing his best.
629.
Look at this.
Okay, let me try to make some profit.
Okay.
I got to kill that.
Oh yeah.
Hello.
Those
[groaning and screaming]
suckers got me. I'm down.
Instagram.
How do I
Wow.
>> Requesting
You think?
O there was
I've got everything you need today and
every day.
Please
Make lose control.
>> Why is he playing music?
I'll get copyright.
>> I'll be seeing you again.
>> Come back anytime.
at the soundboard.
>> Get moving.
Okay, till then let me wash my blades
and everything. Be
also the beta ends in 15 minutes.
[screaming]
H.
Huh?
This whole stream I was in FK. What the
heck?
Unlike last time
too.
Hey.
Oh my god.
I need that hammer and
I need to fix the vehicle.
Where is the hammer?
Medium hammer. Ah, it's building only.
Ah, he need wrench.
Uh,
it.
Oh, the other enemy team is getting all
luck.
Are they retaking
B or what?
Wait, what did what just got landed
right now?
Oh, supplies.
It's me. [\h__\h]
So yeah, let's go respawn and like fix
the vehicle.
At least I'll get some XP from that,
right?
Oh god, there's enemy on the base of
the timing. I had to.
So, what's it going to be?
Hey, backpack required.
Ah, I lost my backpack.
Oh,
>> approach your position.
>> Looks like that cash is burning a hole
in your pocket, pal.
Move it. Time is money.
Okay.
>> Drop me here.
>> Oh, wait. The ACP is destroyed. [\h__\h]
It's 5:00.
Isn't the server about to end?
Ah, the green team is going to win. What
the hell?
And they did destroy the SUP. Okay.
No, thank you.
Oh [\h__\h] Okay,
>> thank you. Thank you.
>> Jo want to play. Uh, wait. The beta is
ending now, though. Bacon.
Like 8 a.m. UTC. It's going to end right
now. 5:00 p.m.
Wait, can you open the game and check if
if we can still play, then we can play?
Yeah.
and we can play
if you're in the lobby. Okay. Okay.
Okay. This match will end in a few
minutes.
Shisha, thank you.
Huh?
and this
you know bacon. You know what happened
today from this game? I was and stuff.
Okay. And my roommate going killed. I
was in the plane at like a helicopter
and and I fist killed my teammate and
and the teammate was like raging at me
in the team chat,
bro. It was so crazy.
It was so funny
as well.
We need some [\h__\h] help over here.
That's okay.
>> Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
[\h__\h]
What? Uh, so I Yeah, I actually my
teammate guy just killed me right after
I
survive.
I'll give you everything.
Survive. Could I say?
>> Yeah, my loader was like fully maxed
out. Fine.
Stop looting me, bro.
He's looting me. Loading me.
He's looting me.
The AK is so good.
[\h__\h]
Okay, let me get on a call with you.
Hello bacon.
Hello. Hello.
And I died.
How long delay on the stream?
>> There's a delay. There should not be a
delay.
Wow. Uh,
I think there's the line. Maybe not.
Maybe I'm mistaken.
>> What is that? It's 59 on stream.
>> Uh, yeah, it should be the line. Maybe
just me.
>> Yeah,
he's like,
>> "Sorry, the game is Skype fight. I
played a little bit today." But the
thing is, your team need to know how to
play.
Yep. And I pre-ordered it.
I
>> actually pre-ordered it.
>> You pre-ordered you crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> To think about to think about your
credit score, Chuck.
>> I know
[laughter]
>> those credit those credit are not yours,
Chuck.
Yeah, you're right.
>> Think about it.
>> Yeah, you're right about that. Wait,
>> did did you buy marathon? You did,
right?
>> Yes.
>> Ah [\h__\h] we haven't even played.
>> God, I have to re I'm going to play next
season, season three.
You got to spend money to make money,
>> I think. Yeah. One more point for the
green and it's over. Wait, how are you
able to play the game? It should be over
though, like Twitter.
>> Uh, I don't know.
>> I think
>> the game maybe. Yeah, bunch of server is
still here. Let me go to the region and
see
uh Asia West.
Yeah, there's still a bunch of in Asia
East.
Still a bunch.
Oh, my fees just froze. No.
Wait, can you still hear me?
>> No.
>> Oh, no. I can't hear you.
Yeah,
>> I can't hear you, Chuck.
>> What?
Wait, wait, wait.
Did you know that I asked to what?
>> Yes, I can still hear you.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my god. [laughter]
>> Okay, well done.
Done with the game.
>> The game
shut down.
Uh yeah, my internet is going bad. Oh
god,
the WhatsApp.
>> Okay, let me check Twitter.
>> It say Sunday at 8
8:00.
>> Saturday today. Oh, Sunday.
>> Is it?
>> Never mind.
It's Sunday.
>> 8:00.
>> 8:00. What?
>> 8:00 UTC.
>> Um,
>> 8:00 p.m. A.M.
>> 8
a.m. UTC.
>> Yeah, it is same day. Sunday.
5 p.m.
weird.
Let me leave match.
The thing is you need people to play or
else you're
doing your own thing.
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
It's like they'reing it to be like,
"Yeah, you got to make friends."
>> It's pretty much like marathon to be
honest.
>> It is.
>> Yeah. Like you need someone to play with
or else like the random people is kind
of a pain in the ass.
>> Yeah. What do you want to go?
>> Uh just play yours.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
Um
98 98 99 99
>> 93 maybe
>> 34
>> 93
>> 34 Yeah. Yeah. Wait. 34 is 99.
Let's go with
>> a [\h__\h]
>> Let's go with I just saw a 95.
Yeah. Uh, let's go with 856.
>> Let's go 96.
>> 95 85.
>> Yeah. Yeah. 85. 85.
>> 85.
>> Bam.
>> Why is it not okay?
>> Oh, there we go.
>> The button was buggy.
>> Oh no. Is it done?
>> Is it done?
>> No. Is it done?
>> Is it on?
>> No.
>> It's back to the the the the
thing, right? the menu.
What do you call it?
[\h__\h] Oh, I think it's done.
>> The title screen. Wait, let me watch
some Let me check Twitch.
Oh my god. No.
>> A man.
>> Is it over? Actually, there are still
people playing their games.
Cuz I think
after you're done with your with the
game, I don't think you can join.
>> Wait, Peanut is still playing.
>> Damn.
Could not retrieve game data from
servers. Oh my god, it's actually done.
>> Let me
>> All right. All right. All right. Europe
is slowly shut Oh, yeah. It's shutting
down.
>> Ah,
>> it's over,
>> man.
>> Kick me in middle of the game.
Ah, that was a good one.
I can't believe like yesterday I forgot
I had a call 900 p.m. and I was like
8:40.
>> Oh my god. Oh, is that there?
>> Yeah. 8:40 p.m. And I was like, "Yeah,
I'm going to wrap up." Then I saw the
message from the collab host like
they're joining the VC and everything.
I'm like, "Oh [\h__\h] I forgot."
>> Yeah.
>> Crazy.
>> Oh, at least you you guys streamed. When
did you meet them?
>> H
>> Where did you meet them?
>> Uh it was like the part two of the big
walk collab.
>> Uh I mean like where where do you find
them?
Japanese YouTuber, right?
>> Uh there are English freaking YouTubers,
too.
[clears throat]
>> Uh how how to say it? I Yeah, I found it
from found them from Twitter.
It's like really rare I feel like
finding people who wants to like
um you know talk with
>> stream
>> yeah to stream and talk with like
Japanese people etc.
>> Not Japanese foreigners etc.
>> It's rare.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. Not everyone wants to do that. I
realize that. Man, remember you did have
one Japanese YouTuber
stream with you before, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. For the Joan. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I reached out to some people that
was
at Sheran.
Yeah. And recently I re another one
>> Joathon
>> from Joon. That was a long long
>> Yeah.
>> sound like a long history ago.
>> Exactly. A long history ago.
>> It's only a year, but this feel like so
long ago.
>> Exactly.
>> And it's over.
like one match is really
[music]
>> I mean
never mind.
>> Welcome to
you haven't finished even finished
Welcome to Koon.
>> Ah yeah that game. You
>> remember that horror game I gave it to
you?
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Ah the scary game.
>> You play that game?
Welcome.
>> Welcome to Cal.
This look good though. Damn.
Ah, the game is over playing.
wanted to play more. Uh,
I mean, what do you think of Did you see
the FPS game show?
>> FBF game show.
>> Uh, no.
>> I also couldn't watch it fully, but it
was nice. I guess
>> there's so many new games.
Right now I'm trying to finish uh
expedition 33.
>> I'm planning to make a video about it.
>> Oh, let's go.
>> That is so nice.
>> I don't know, man. Right now, power is
just too addicted to me. I already have
120 hours
>> on on par or like expedition
>> world.
>> Yeah, power is
want to play Destiny 2.
>> Destiny.
>> I finished playing Destiny.
>> What do you What do you mean you
finished?
>> Finish. That's like it's like a game
which cannot be finished, right? There's
so many stuff to do.
>> You grind.
>> Oh, they're done. They stop, right?
Remember
>> the game? The game is finished now.
They're done. Done with Destiny 2.
>> Destiny 2.
>> You don't know
>> what? It's over.
>> Yeah, it's over.
Major actor development for Destin is
over following finaliz update on June
9th 2036.
>> What?
>> Two months ago, no 3 months ago.
>> Play it just like the original way.
>> What?
It's over.
>> So Destiny 3 is coming. [laughter]
>> No,
>> they are pouring. They they they living
on life support uh with Marathon
>> and Mar Marathon barely get any player
now day. So it's kind of sucks. And
Marathon is such a good game but people
just hate it so much.
>> Yeah. Such that's a shame.
>> True. True.
They mostly they mostly hate it because
it's bungee,
>> but still the game is it's just so cool.
I love the game so much.
>> Even though I don't play much these days
cuz I'm so busy.
>> 327 hours. Damn.
Damn.
>> For what?
>> Marathon. Ah,
crazy.
>> 267
for our greater and barely play the
game.
>> I do our greatest
>> I think people R has such a fall fall
what's the word fall down.
>> Yeah.
>> What what what is that word?
It fell off.
>> No, but but yeah, it fell off. Yeah,
it fell so hard.
Still because it's uh extraction
shooter, right? It's a niche. It's a
niche game. So,
>> I saw what happened to our greatest and
I was like, wow.
>> Oh, hey. But still the for a stand for
like a genre like extra shooter right
now they have 30k players that is no
wait is it 16k right now that is a still
a good number for for a extraction
shooter
mostly extraction shooter games just uh
around 10,000
below 10,000
Just a few thousand
at most.
>> Also, wait, you can make custom servers.
What?
>> For what?
>> For Warog custom custom
uh servers.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Wow. Peanut Peanut made a custom server
due to stream snipers.
Crazy
>> peanuts.
Uh
peanut. Peanut. Peanut.
>> Do you watch Peanut his streams?
>> Nah,
>> I did watch him back in Arrator. No, no.
>> Yeah, I also used to watch him daily
during AR era.
That was really nice.
>> What's your overall
>> Minecraft?
>> Minecraft. You don't have Minecraft?
Nope, I don't.
>> Um,
I get it.
>> Tea launcher. Tea launcher for 10 years.
>> Oh my [laughter] god.
>> You just buy it.
>> What? What was your question?
>> I was like, what was it? What was my
question? I forgot. Uh,
oh my god, I just forgot. What? Yeah.
What are your thoughts of Warog?
That's a cool game.
>> Slow pace,
>> but it has it needs a lot of teamwork.
If you like play it properly, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> If you just play it for like for fun and
chill, it's it's okay. But when you play
it like seriously and really into the
game, it's
>> it's kind of get frustrated because
you're
debuting.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's it's really need a lot of
teamwork.
True.
I think
>> so. It kind of sucks.
>> Kind of kind of sucks.
>> Okay. [music]
>> I think I kept on what do you call it?
I think I kept on like
um I mean the real the game I feel like
it's not just shooting, it's other
things too which is nice, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Like helicopter thingy.
>> Yeah. As long as you you have fun
playing it. Yeah. Like you can be like
just do a helicopter just transport
people. That's just a chill chill role.
M
>> you only need to shoot.
>> The truck and the driving was nice.
>> Yeah, but too much driving.
>> I was making money like from the
helicopter supplies which drops on the
force base, right?
>> I just buy everything and just put it
into force
base. I I [clears throat] earned a lot
of money from that. That was [music]
nice.
Most people are have 1 million or 10
million stuff already.
Crazy.
>> I don't know how to do that. People are
making so much money.
It's just so crazy.
It's the sweaty pupil.
>> Yeah,
>> sweaty pupil
>> exactly.
Uh,
so what are you up to?
>> I don't know. About to sleep.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm
>> planning to play one game with you and
then you go to sleep. sleep.
>> It's 4:00 a.m. here.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Yeah, you should sleep. Oh, yeah.
Tomorrow is Monday. No,
>> you got work.
>> I don't want to sleep.
>> Wait, is it
Sunday for you?
>> It's Sunday for me.
>> Sunday. Sunday. or
>> the school done for you for now
>> or
>> I have a class on Monday.
>> School done for you.
>> It's not done done. I have
>> Oh,
>> classes on Monday.
>> Like were you were you were you on uh
what do you call it? Summer break or
something? Oh, that's over.
Next break is coming on September
September or like uh forgot when is the
next break.
October or something. It's coming like
just one week or two week.
>> Mhm.
>> Ow. Ow. Oh, my leg. Ah.
>> Oh. September 26th to October 5th. And
this
and that's a week.
Just a just a week.
Not bad. [laughter]
Probably have to work over time. Like
not over time, like extra work hours
during vacation time.
>> 40 hours.
>> Still working at the
>> No, I got a restaurant job, so I'm doing
both. Yeah. Yeah. I'm doing both.
>> 15 hours on the old place and the
>> Yeah.
>> rest remaining hours and I'll get it
from the new place. So
>> 40 hours during school.
>> No, no, no. 28.
>> 28 during school
>> in a week.
>> Hey. Okay. Okay.
>> Yes.
>> You have like a lot of uh assignment.
assignment. No assignment.
>> Then that's good
>> cuz back in my school time there's just
so many freaking assigns and I told my
boss to just get 18 hours.
>> Mhm.
>> But they uh
will allowed me is uh 24 hours. So
>> many hours every weeks should last me or
let me save enough for
rent
and other expenses.
>> Oh, wait. The game comes out on
>> Oh, is that new?
>> Not not new. It's been there for a
while. I think it's like a seafood
Japanese cuisine restaurant.
I just serve uh this thing and
everything. Yeah.
>> What what what restaurant is it?
>> Uh the name is funny. It's called
Bikini.
[laughter]
>> Huh?
>> Yeah.
>> Say that again.
>> Bikini.
>> What bikini?
>> That's the name of the restaurant.
Just bikini.
Bikini restaurant.
>> Oh, with capital. Okay.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
Japan.
>> Also, have you
>> a seafood place? And do you understand
how to use the molar? How does that
work? How do you figure out the
meters and everything and get the the
right?
>> So the vertical thing it's the vertical
thing is uh the the travel what the
length
>> travel distance. Huh?
>> Like it's Yeah. distance. Distant. Yeah.
And
>> yeah, that I think that's all you need
to know.
Ah
>> but for aiming [music] where to get it
but that one I don't know I just shoot
it randomly. I just shoot it randomly.
>> Like I just guess the distance like at
first you
>> my guess is just ping ping on the map
first and then
>> look at the ping and see how far is it
and then just try to the direction.
>> That's my guess.
>> Bikini bikini sis.
It has a lot of menus and everything, so
I have to learn the menu. And
>> damn, it's fancy.
>> It is fancy. Yeah.
>> Wait, why is my stream
>> How much are they paying you? Is that
minimum wage?
>> Minimum wage. Same same rate as the
first job.
>> Oh, yeah. It sucks.
I should have asked for
>> Were you going to race if you like
worked that long? Yeah, apparently.
Yeah, that's a thing I asked.
>> They don't speak don't speak English.
>> Nope.
>> I mean, the chef looks white.
>> Oh my god.
>> It's a Spanish restaurant, right? It's
>> not a Spanish restaurant.
Wait, am I looking at the right one?
Bikini sis, right? S I S. Wait, let me
give you the
uh restaurant.
You know what? I'll give you the
website. That's way better.
There you go.
My god, if I got hacked.
>> My god. It's all It's all Japanese.
>> Yeah, it's all Japanese.
>> But as you can see, like the food and
everything. It comes with a set. So to
say the names of all these food and the
restaurant is like a closed place space
where with a big table and like some mad
like cushions and you sit down.
>> So I serve these dishes and name
serve it to them and then leave.
Holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
>> My god.
Search up the name the name of the
restaurant and I click click uh images.
Just show me all ladies in bikini for
[\h__\h] sake.
Oh my god. What would you call it?
Bikini
[laughter]
bikini restaurant. [music]
>> I know
>> it's not even slightly a bikini editing
in here.
>> There's no reason for them to
put that name.
>> Bikini Khan. I [music] think that's
Bikini Khan.
>> Bikini Khan. Yeah,
>> Bikini Khan.
Uh, am I looking at the right place?
Oh, there's no images. Oh, there is
here.
Yeah, it's not bikini. It's bikini con
jo.
It's It's look middle middle class.
Yeah, it's not too fancy fancy. It looks
standard. Yeah, quite standard. Yeah.
>> Or Japanese sushi place.
>> It is interesting though.
I kind of sometimes feel like
>> I don't know why like um I was like
watching bit of uh the peanut stream and
it got raided to the 24x channel of
peanuts. Man, I miss my 24x7 channel
thingy out of nowhere.
I I kind of wish I could control my PC
from India. That's what that was my
plan. Okay, control my PC from India and
make my dad turn it on and I run the 24x
on channel. But o, I can't do it. Sucks.
Yeah, it's it's kind of sad like what if
something happened
from the at the PC, right? You can't go
back and fix it.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah,
man. I did.
This place [music] sucks.
I realized there's a lot of
Oh [\h__\h]
The stream is streaming.
Oh my god.
>> Wait, what?
>> It's
Oh, they're watching my stream. Oh [\h__\h]
I I was like uh looking
Was
it not streaming or what?
What?
>> Wait, what channel? What channel?
Wait, what? How do they know? Are they
like randomly checking you or you just
comment? What? What the [\h__\h]
How' that happen?
Oh, you followed them. So, they just
check your camera.
Uh
uh.
>> Oh my god.
>> Uh
oh.
Say
I had to write it in Japanese. Yeah.
Yes. I'm learning Japanese. I'm a
language student.
Language.
>> Is it on Twitch?
>> Oh, yes. Yes. Yes.
In Japan.
Yes, I was playing War. It was really
fun.
Uh, all right.
Uh, ring.
Oh, that's Oh, God. This
Let me center the thing.
That was
>> what?
Oh my god. Okay.
>> Hello.
>> YouTuber on YouTube.
[laughter]
How do you say friend?
My tommoachi
jock son.
Uh
[laughter]
>> oh my god. Don't say something out
there.
>> I'm I'm glazing you here. M
got the
follow sub.
>> I might have to speak in Japanese. No.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
[clears throat] I
got the
I just randomly found this person's
channel
and yeah, I I just don't just follow
Lord. I didn't expect that.
Uh
by goodbye.
Oh yeah. How was your day overall?
My hurts leg. My my legs hurt. The hell?
What did I say? My hurts leg. My legs
hurt.
>> Hurts leg.
>> Yeah, I was playing soccer. It's been
like 3 years since I like exercised some
intensely.
>> So,
so a few days ago was my first day back
doing any sort of heavy exercise.
Mhm.
>> So I play play I play with the pace of
how I used to play like back when I'm
still kind of being athletic and stuff.
So my body just cannot keep up now. Now
I'm now I'm just in [\h__\h] pain.
My whole body, every muscle is pain is
burned. So I just lay on bed all day.
Dude, I can't even pull my freaking
pants normally.
Today I just woke up and wanted to
man I really want to go out but my place
there's not much stuff to do.
It's just like trees.
Who riverly
care house
kind of lame?
It's just like a town.
I want to go back to the city.
I want that city.
Hustle and bustle.
Light cars, vehicle everywhere.
>> They were like looking for someone to
raid and actually saw my channel or
something. They followed me. I felt so
bad.
But
>> looking what? They're looking for
someone to raid. Yeah, I I just was I
kept um their stream in the background
>> so I can watch while um while having uh
like lunch
like I was watching some W dog streamers
like people streaming W dogs who are
Japanese so I could like know which
server they're joining.
Mhm.
>> Which which which platform you get more
more view? Twitch or YouTube or cake
>> lately? Twitch. Usually
>> usually well
usually I think
I think it's Twitch I think. Not not
sure
on Twitch there are some people who come
by and stuff
and YouTube lately not much people are
coming I don't know what happened
>> current viewer location for [\h__\h] sake
is it just [\h__\h] docs my location
for [\h__\h] sake jock
got two people from America watching you
right now. America.
America.
>> Wait, two people watching from America?
What? Really?
>> Yeah. Look down.
>> Or my
>> just one person from Canada. I wonder
who. One person from India.
>> Yeah.
>> Two people from freaking USA.
>> America.
Two people from America.
Okay.
Uh I I think I barely have any um
American viewers.
Back in the days I used to have some
people come by. I wonder what happened
to them.
>> Also, do you want to play Wait, no. Um,
do you want to play escape of I think
that's a old game now, but have you ever
wanted to play escape from? Yeah,
another
>> extraction.
>> Too much too much. Too much extraction
shooter.
They're already playing marathon and not
raider. Well, mostly marathon now.
dancing in September
that that streamer son ended their
stream.
Ah, nice.
>> Go back. No raid for you.
>> No, no, I didn't I didn't want the raid
myself. I was like really surprised that
they actually opened up my Twitch
account and checked and they noticed
that I was live. And also I realized
that I need to
>> change my about
page on Twitch and make it Japanese too
with those who can't read English now.
Yeah, I need to do that.
Yeah.
Oh, wait. My stream is Oh my god. Again.
Wait. How come my stream is dying? Wait.
What? What? What? What? What?
It's like 10 minutes behind.
Ah, stream is
stream is 4 minutes.
>> Don't ask me, bro. [music]
>> Behind
a new stream. Any schedule?
Uh, not really. I just wing it.
I found the uh Yeah. Okay. The secret
trick to fix my internet. Go back to the
Wi-Fi router's Ethernet port and just
shake it. Ah, [\h__\h] Jinxed it. No.
>> Shake it.
>> No, I I just shake the wire.
Ah, I jinxed it back to red. Okay, it's
fixed. [music] I think
[laughter]
indeed.
Lol indeed.
Uh
man, bacon, how how would you tell me
your experience if you wanted people to
play with games and stuff? How do you
make friends and how do you make [music]
connections and stuff?
Uh
>> good question. I don't
>> I don't
>> mostly play play alone and guck
cuz a lot of my friend doesn't play my
game. So
>> there's that too. I noticed that too.
>> So I'll either somehow
>> Yeah. I'll either some somehow drag my
girlfriend to play with me or just play
alone. Uh-huh.
>> Like for example, marathon. Marathon.
You you're the only one of any of my
friend that play this kind of genre.
>> Other than that, no one plays this kind
of genre.
>> Yeah. Most of the time just play alone.
>> Okay. The stream is now fixed. Yay. Now
it's back to red. of
like
pain.
But yeah,
I'm I I wish I can find people who speak
Japanese and how I'm playing with you,
right? We play and live and play any
games we like. We both have and we play
and have a good time like that. If there
was a Japanese dude too, that'll be so
nice.
All right. Speak Japanese. They English
learning as well.
>> Find one eventually.
>> I hope I'll find
>> There's a lot of uh nihongo du that
really want to do Japanese stuff.
[music] I mean, English stuff. I'm sure
of it.
>> Yeah.
Just need to find just need to dig for
them.
>> Yep.
>> You know how nihongo people are
[laughter]
>> people.
>> I am not racist. I am not generalizing.
I'm just being sarcastic.
Go men. Hi to anyone offended.
>> Go men. Go men.
>> I don't know why I f I feel
>> I I miss water dogs now. Wow.
I want to play.
>> Just wait four more days, dude. Four
more days.
>> Four more days.
Wow. Crazy. It's too much.
Four more days is like so many days. I
feel like
four or more days. Wow.
What? What? Yorkie Chan.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm train.
I'm training to be a Yakuza.
Who's that?
>> Yeah, I'll I'll get a full body tattoo
soon.
>> Okay, then see later next. Hi. Take
care. Hey, take care.
Thanks for
dropping that.
>> Well, well, well.
>> The Elgato. It's so good. My [\h__\h]
quality, stream quality, it's so good.
Holy [\h__\h]
It's so smooth.
Like, I'm able to stream in 2K because
of this thing. Damn.
The [\h__\h] was that?
Okay, I'm back.
Ah,
>> hello.
Hello. Hello.
Um,
Switch games with download.
>> Wait, what shooter games do you have
right now?
>> What? What?
>> What shooter games do you have right now
on PC?
You install AR, right? Um,
>> a maton.
>> Yeah,
>> I have to install it. O,
>> I'm downloading Battlefield. I want to
see how how's the game right now. I
haven't played like
>> you have VF6
>> 5 months.
Yeah, BF6.
>> Should I get it?
[laughter]
>> I don't know because the the review is
very mixed right now. It's good when
when it first launched, but I I think
it's kind of went
fell off. Fell really fell off very
hard.
>> Yeah, it's falling off. I guess
I'm really conflicted. Like, should I
like like Ward Dogs? Okay, it's a new
game. It's like I'm treating it like our
greatest. The hype is there.
>> Play for a bit. See how it goes.
Maybe. Nah,
>> something like that.
>> I wouldn't recommend it.
>> I mean, body cam is fun. [\h__\h] Did I buy
body cam?
>> Mhm.
>> You have body cam, right?
>> Yeah, I do have body cam. Yes.
>> God damn.
my next paycheck.
And then my next paycheck.
Guess I still have my credit debt.
[laughter]
This credit [\h__\h] man. My next paycheck,
I'll pay all my I paid all my debt and I
stop using my credit card, man. It's
>> It's scary.
>> Damn.
>> It just give you a false sense of
[music] being rich.
>> Mhm.
Why are there so many not safe for word
game on Steam? Stop.
>> There is so many.
>> Wow.
>> You don't know. Probably you got like
the the filter on. I don't think I don't
have the filter on. So there's so
>> so many. [laughter]
>> I think I got the filter on.
>> I mean what
Call of Duty Black Op 3 it's 75% sale
now if you interest
>> I
>> 20 bucks. My bad. I honestly wanted to
pre-book Call of Duty
Modern Warfare 4 too, but
>> I don't know.
>> No, don't
don't.
>> That's the That would be the dumbest
financial move you could do.
like
battlefield.
I don't know. A battlefield is
nice, but
what happened though? I don't really
know what happened.
>> I don't know. I I I'm like feeling
conflicted to should I go with white
Battlefield? Is it fun anymore and
stuff? I mean,
when you look at it, not much people are
playing it, too. It's just sad,
right? How it used to be, right?
Let's just read the review after I'm
done defending this game after putting
60 hour plus into it and waiting for
blah blah blah blah blah. Oh,
>> it's painful. Obvious. The game is
completely rotten as it [music] core.
Uh,
awful mad design. Sound and basic polish
are broken. Audio is a joke. The UI is
atrocious.
Not really.
But apparently they um they removed a
lot of game mode from the game
>> without like uh any reason pretty much.
>> It's like Destiny removing their their
DLC.
>> Yeah,
>> that people paid [music] for.
>> I don't know why. I don't know how to
say it. I feel like I'm bad at when it
comes to these big large maps. Large
maps are nice, but it's like you spawn
it's like league. You spawn from the
base and you have to walk all the way to
the fighting area.
I respect.
It's okay.
Oh, wait. Do you have GTA 5?
>> Nope.
>> I'm not a big GTA map person.
What time do I work tomorrow?
God damn.
>> Oh, yeah. Work tomorrow. What time?
>> I'm sorry.
>> What time?
>> Uh,
well, tomorrow. Tomorrow. Like Monday?
It's like 4:00 a.m. Sunday here. So, I
have [music] a whole day, so I don't
need to.
>> Ah, it's Sunday for you.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Uh
>> uh starting my new job too. God damn.
>> Starting my new job next week. [snorts]
>> Ahm
What do
you think?
Louise is precious. Who is this person?
Oh, I'm getting
some new employee here. Okay. Okay.
>> New employee.
Wow.
>> No, like like new Indian employee. Yeah,
there's a few Indian employee in my
place.
>> Oh,
>> one of them. I'm close. I'm pretty close
with them.
>> Oh, yeah. You're not playing uh
like you're not
um playing Valerant anymore.
>> Nope. Cuz I don't have anyone here to
play with.
>> Yeah, but
>> kind of sucks.
>> Yeah, true.
Wait, do you remember how we met?
you
right
>> that's how I met you right
>> mostly
>> theor
through
>> through state I think
>> yeah state
>> yeah theor
stops
>> yep now they butchered my champion
[\h__\h] hell
>> you see the changes for yoro do you do
You see?
>> No, I haven't. So, I haven't seen it.
>> Like, you only have one flash like bad
bad.
Come on.
Oh, wait. Wonder what other people are
doing in the warox category.
Let me check.
Ah, not much people are there. No,
that's in Japan. Okay, sorry.
Everyone is like
going through clips or something.
Damn.
Oh, yeah. Did you get the
Did you get the
word dogs? Uh, did you watch any streams
on Twitch? Like, did you get like the
Warox chat badge
for free?
>> Nope.
>> I just played the game.
>> That's nice.
>> Heading to bed now. It's 5 a.m.
>> Yes.
All right, J. Thanks for um playing, I
guess. [laughter]
>> Well, I wish we could have played one
game at least, but O.
>> Yeah, bad timing, I guess.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. See you, Jack.
>> Hi. See you. What's up?
>> Just tell me.
>> Yeah. Text me if you want to play
anything.
>> Surely. Surely. Yes.
>> All right. See you.
>> Bye. See you.
Wait, that was bread everyone. Hello.
Hello. What's
Wait, why did I say hello?
Why did I say hello? Wow.
No. Um,
what do we do?
Um,
no. Uh for those uh who are who are
thinking, "Oh, doc, will you be playing
this game when it comes out on September
10th?" The answer to that question is
yes, I will be playing it cuz I have
pre-ordered the game.
And this Thursday or Friday, Saturday,
Sunday, this Saturday, Sunday, we going
to be playing this. Yeah, of course. Of
course.
going to be playing that. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm excited for that. Yes.
And next. Um,
one second.
Okay. Um, what else? Um,
there is collab highlight. Uh,
um,
ready for everyone. 100 player FP
shorter.
I just wish like
I just wish like um what is that?
I just wish like um those doesn't
fall off.
That's
just hope.
Yeah, it's a good great game. It's fun
and
yeah,
really nice.
And uh yeah, literally now I think we
should switch categories on Twitch.
I'll change categories on Twitch. Let's
change to just chatting. Okay.
Um, I don't want to end the stream here.
We'll do a just starting segment. Okay.
Um, I know I've been live for 3 hours. I
could I know, but yeah.
Or I could start the I could put a
separate stream or a just chatting
segment where I talk about
um what is it? the VTuber concert stuff
other stuffs I wanted to do YouTuber
concert stuff which I wanted to talk
about show pictures or something should
we do that today or should we
do that next time
I don't know yeah
so then
or They have until badge upgrade. What
is this?
Wait, did I get a gifting thingy on
Twitch?
Cuz I gifted.
I think I got a gifting gift thingy,
right? Uh, I think I do.
Yeah. I wanted I really wanted the
I really wanted the um what do you call
it?
The Vardog's golden badge. So I
I kind of like um
uh
Yeah, I kind of like um God and
like
kind of like got and like um
wait what was it saying? F [laughter]
I saw some tweet and I got distracted.
[\h__\h]
I want to play a game.
I'm streaming on YouTube. So, um I'm
having I have to like end the YouTube
stream and make a new one. Something
like that.
But yeah, um I know I've been recently
been just uh streaming h streaming
streaming. I don't wish to like do more
stuff. It's just that I don't get much
time that I like I'm used to having
before.
So this
my internet is failing me. For what
reason? For what reason?
3,000 bit rate is not able to
sustain it. What?
Why isn't the net bad today?
Do I have any comments on Twitch? No to
Twitter. Okay. Okay. The stream is
running. Okay. Is there a delay here and
there? Okay, that's fine. I do boo.
You didn't believe it. Like if Warog
didn't happen. No, I was like, "Yeah,
Call of Duty
season and now Warog season and I
actually bought the game. So, it's going
to be a longer season
of FPS gaming and stuff." [music]
And one match takes so much hours. So
you can expect me to like play one game
of War Dog's her stream and play till
the end or something
which is interesting.
But yeah,
uh
I wish I could move my model man. I
could show my expressions and stuff like
when we were gaming and stuff. Now I was
making so much I was
>> [laughter]
>> I keep forgetting that. Yeah, I don't
have a live 2D. I was like making some
uh expressions and stuff. I was like,
"Hey,
not today's stream. Yesterday's stream
actually."
Mhm.
What the
I have to do more GP practicing
for this.
Mhm.
Oh.
Um.
Oh, here. And what is this?
Could it
stream clock
copy or put it in obvious I guess.
Wait, I can actually do.
Oh, I can actually do that.
down the glass. Uh,
wait, how does my stream? Okay, that
let me say capsule.
Okay, I found like a new um
uh
Okay, it's fine. Hi.
Hold on there.
by
I will um
probably
wrap it off soon, I guess. Here.
I think that is better for now.
Oh, the snap.
I wanted to buy Battlefield 6, but I
don't know if I should.
If it's fun and all, I will do it.
You know, I can't buy it. I'm at broke
right now as I shouldn't.
Yeah.
Now, if you were to ask me like, Jun,
uh, will you only be streaming FPS
games? What about other types of games?
Don't worry ever. I have plans to do
that as long as I can
find some time
to
like um specifically speaking like there
is so much to do for jo
and I'm like cuz I'm doing these streams
here and there. I'm like not like not
actually
doing it. uh pro like the priorities.
So it's kind of
so it's kind of if I if
FBI.
Oh, yeah. This must doesn't have like
lighting. I forgot.
There's no RGB in this mouse I have.
Yeah,
all right. Um, we'll wrap it up by 6:30.
Okay. So, I got a few more minutes with
you guys.
So, yeah. Um,
those who actually my streams
appreciative of it. I'm really thankful.
Thank you. So,
and it means the world to me.
Okay, I know I was not talking much and
everything cuz again it's really hard,
you know, um
to balance it when you're in a when
you're in a dometry and you have your
room working
beside me and I'm like too shy to talk
and everything.
Okay.
[music]
In this
place green clock.
Okay.
I got kid. That's
I'm looking at Twitter.
Okay. So, uh let me wrap it off. Uh not
wrap it off like that. Talk about things
I guess. So, remaining things I have
left to do. Uh one is the website. Two
is got to do Oh yeah, my chat G ended. I
had a one year free subscription now cuz
I was in India and um
the subscription stuff, right? Oh yeah,
I forgot about that.
Uh,
damn it. Forgot about you.
November 5.
Hey, wait a minute.
It's November 5th. Not
uh then I have time. Oh my god.
What?
Yeah, this corner plan renews on October
5th. Huh?
Interest.
Let's
see how that goes. There's a few things
I have working on.
I'll get those stuff done soon.
Um
due to today's stuff, I realized that I
have to change my about panel and
everything.
Um,
so it's easier for people to understand
uh what I do and everything,
right?
So that's all
there's so much things, bro. I don't
know. It's too
And those who are lurking, thank you for
lurking. It means the world to me. Thank
you again.
And um
yeah, I've been thinking recently I
should do something about my
24x7 voice channel stuff.
I don't know if it's worth it even to
like, you know,
buy a small server and like somehow
stream website stuff on it. Will it
work? I don't know.
Um, I've been having thoughts about
that.
Maybe it would work, maybe it won't
work. Who knows? Let's see.
Good work. Could not work.
Free plan
$40 per month stream
upstream zone. I have to look into this.
Yeah, I had to do something about the
stream chats as well. That's that also
needs some things
uh fixing.
Ah, you know, it's Sunday. I'll have I
have some time. So, I'll just maybe uh
do that maybe.
Uh
yeah. And also one more thing is that I
need a I need a
um
I need to start
making short form content and everything
and I miss doing vlogs and IRL streams.
I want to do that too.
Yeah.
Well, we'll we'll get it done
for you.
What do you want me?
Uh, I'll check this uh off stream. Okay,
I'll have to end the stream. So, yeah,
thank you to everyone who came by today.
Uh, thank you Kadasan. Thank you. Um,
thank you for the follows on Twitch. It
is
Nar. Thank you. And also com
thank you for giving me a shout out
didn't have to but thank you Amberan and
Danti Fox on yesterday for the followers
and stuff. Thank you so much and yeah
I believe um we got everyone else. We've
got a lot of people.
Uh but then let me adjust my audio
levels.
Hi.
And I'll start working on stuff today.
I'll be productive.
Oh, if I wanted to, I can. I mean, yeah,
I have to upload yesterday's stream. Two
stream boards to Billy. I'll just do
that. I have it downloaded before
sleeping yesterday. So, this stream too
is going to be downloaded, uploaded on
Billy. I got to make videos for Billy. I
got to make videos for YouTube, Twitch,
all those stuff.
I'll try. I give it my best. Okay. can't
promise things because again my time is
limited so I could only do a few things
uh whatever I can at the time. So yeah
but yeah with that said
and thank you for today. Have a good
one. Thank you, Bacon, for joining me
today and having fun and talking with me
as well. Hi
What's so